These moldings here I tend to use in a cowboy type thoughts.
This particular one here I used around a lady who had won her ribbon for roping a cow.
They had a picture of her roping the cow, the cow that helped her win the ribbon.
Her husband is a great cowboy, he is very cowboy he wears cowboy hat, blue jeans, boots the whole bit.
And she told me I need this to hang in my husbands office and you know how much of a cowboy he is.
So I got to looking at the picture and decided that I wanted to use this with it cause it just look like him.
Several of these are the same way they are very much cowboy looking.
They fit in other things as well but I tend to reach for them often when I'm dealing with my cowboy people or my country people.
Because they just fit it is a very earthy frame.
Most cowboys are very earthy people, people are very earthy people and they tend to lean not as fancy as thought.
This is actually something that you can put around a document, you can put it around a photo or put it around a piece of art, and it is going to fit in almost everyones home.